thelightforge.com 2018-07-29

# Lightforge - PrivacyPolicy

TheLightforge.com owned and operated by GrinningGoat is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This privacy statement explains The Lightforge’s data collection and use practices with respect to its website (the “Site”). By using the pages in this site, you agree to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

## Collection of Personal Information

The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the Site. This information is used, among other things, to help improve the Site, analyze use trends and administer the Site. 

## Use of Personal Information

Except as otherwise required by law, the personal information collected on this Site will be used solely to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) and/or product(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. In support of these purposes, The Lightforge may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related The Lightforge products or services. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with The Lightforge, information collected by the Site may be combined with information collected in connection with other The Lightforge products and services.

The Lightforge may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Lightforge or the Site; or (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Lightforge and the Site.

## Security of Personal Information

The Lightforge is strongly committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

## Cookies

We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server and that helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

The use of cookies simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and provides other similar benefits to users of the Site. When you return to the Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Site's features. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site.

## DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## Links to Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites. The Lightforge is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Changes to this Statement

We reserve the right to update this privacy statement from time to time. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement, as amended from time to time.

## Contact Information

The Lightforge welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that The Lightforge has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us electronically at the following email address, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem:

E-mail: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
